Neymar John

CONTACT

Address: Fo ter 20, Tatabanya. Komárom-Esztergom,

Hungary

Mail:superdeveloper0217@gmail.comGit:https://github.com/neymarjohnSkype:live:.cid.foo1faea3ab92d58

SKILLS

• Code and Quality Standards

- Blockchain Development
- Database Management Software
- Project Management
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- JS Frameworks: React, Angular, Vue
- Code Analysis and Development
- Software Testing and Validation
- Programming Languages
- Source and Version Control: Git, Github
- Team Management
- Algorithm design and structure

Senior Full Stack & Web3 engineer offering over 9 years of experience in web application development, blockchain projects.

Owned an in-depth practical and applicable knowledge of technical subjects from programming languages to modern frameworks for web development.

Worked on Blockchain startups and projects and got hand-on experience in crypto projects.

Possess a demonstrated ability to work on multiple projects independently and as part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

<u>Laguna(NUON)</u> — Senior Web3 Engineer

lan 2022 ~

- Integrated web3.js and ethers.js into React, Next.js and Vue.js web applications for MVP & product version.
- Implemented multiple wallet support using RainbowKit and Wagmi.
- Developed smart contracts with Smart contracts, hardhat and Opeasea.
- Developed The Graph backend for tracking events & storing statistics data.
- Maintained & updated projects according to the business requirements.

Snowball — Web3 Engineer

May 2021 - Dec 2021

- · Integrated ethers.js into React project.
- Wrote contracts for stable vault with lead smart contract developer.
- · Maintained project & updated features

Maryoku — Senior Full-stack Engineer

Oct 2020 - Jun 2021

- · Implemented UI/UX with React and Vue.js
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Developed REST APIs and integrate them into front end applications
- · Design data structure and manage MongoDB Database
- · Deploy web on AWS Lightsail virtual machine and maintain it

RockPeaks — Full-stack Engineer

Oct 2017 - Apr 2020

- Implemented new UI/UX using React, Next.js, SCSS and Bootstrap.
- · Integrated APIs using GraphQL and React Apollo.
- Upgraded and maintained a number for front end projects according to the customers' requirements.
- Developed reusable components with React and Storybook.
- Performed all levels of testing from Unit test to Acceptance test

EDUCATION

University of Debrecen, Debrecen, Egyetem tér 1, 4032 Hungary— Bachelor of Science

May 2009 - May 2013